Downtown Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Photographs, circa 1880-1960s, undated, Series 8:; (Boxes 109-118, OV 119; 8.75 linear ft.; Reels 5647-5654)
  - Black-and-White Negatives, undated, 8.6:
    This subseries contains an incomplete set of negatives for photographs included in the American Folk Art Gallery Notebooks. The negatives were not microfilmed.
    - Portraits Sold (Reel unfilmed (Box 115-Hol 116))
    - Portraits (Reel unfilmed (Box 115-Hol 116))
    - Landscapes Sold (Reel unfilmed (Box 115-Hol 116))
    - Landscapes (Reel unfilmed (Box 115-Hol 116))
    - Genre Sold (Reel unfilmed (Box 115-Hol 116))
    - William Harnett (Reel unfilmed (Box 115-Hol 116))
    - Still Life Sold (Reel unfilmed (Box 115-Hol 116))
    - Trade Signs Sold (Reel unfilmed (Box 115-Hol 116))
    - All Types (Reel unfilmed (Box 115-Hol 116))
    - Steel Pen Drawings (Reel unfilmed (Box 115-Hol 116))
    - Pastels (Reel unfilmed (Box 115-Hol 116))
    - Fraktur (Reel unfilmed (Box 115-Hol 116))
    - Paintings on Velvet (Reel unfilmed (Box 115-Hol 116))
    - Embroideries (Reel unfilmed (Box 115-Hol 116))
    - Sculpture, Chalkware Sold (Reel unfilmed (Box 115-Hol 116))
    - Sculpture, Chalkware, Plaster Ornaments (Reel unfilmed (Box 115-Hol 116))
    - Sculpture, Wood, Birds, Eagles, Animals (Reel unfilmed (Box 115-Hol 116))
    - Sculpture, Wood, Toys (Reel unfilmed (Box 115-Hol 116))
    - Sculpture, Wood, Figures (Reel unfilmed (Box 115-Hol 116))
    - Sculpture, Weather Vanes (Reel unfilmed (Box 115-Hol 116))
    - Unidentifiable Media (Reel unfilmed (Box 115-Hol 116))
  - Color Slides and Glass Plate Negatives, undated, 8.7:
    Color slides and glass plate negatives of works of art by various artists are found in this subseries.
    Arrangement is as follows: negatives by subject category; negatives by artist name, A to Z; negatives by artist name, B to T; and negatives of unidentified artists.
    - American Folk Art (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Blaustein, Al (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Booz, Michelle (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Broderson, Morris (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Darrow, Paul (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Davis, Stuart (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Demuth, Charles (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Doi, Isami (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Dove, Arthur (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Fredenthal, David (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Hartley, Marsden (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Karfiol, Bernard (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Kerciu, G. Ray (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Kuniyoshi, Yasuo (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Levine, Jack (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Marin, John (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Morris, George L. K. (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Norris, Ben (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - O'Keeffe, Georgia (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Opliger, Curt (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Osborn, Robert (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Ottesen, Frederik (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Pattison, Abbott (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Rattner, Abraham (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Shahn, Ben (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Sheeler, Charles (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Spencer, Niles (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Stasack, Edward (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Stella, Joseph (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Storrs, John (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Tseng, Yu-Ho (Betty Ecke) (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Weber, Max (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Wight, Fred (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Zorach, William (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Berry (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Bissier, Jules (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Bloom, Hyman (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Feininger, Lyonel (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Greene, Stephen (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Kinigstein, Jonah (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Knipschild, Robert (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Lawrence, Jacob (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Levi, Julian (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Mattson, Henry (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Miró, Joan (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Price, C. S. (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Takehita, Natsuko (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Tam, Reuben (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Tamayo, Rufino (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Tobey, Mark (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Treiman, Joyce (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))
    - Unidentified Artists (Reel unfilmed (Box 117))